<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1251'?>
<GateDocument version="3">
<!-- The document's features-->

<GateDocumentFeatures>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">gate.SourceURL</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String">file:/C:/Users/mosya/Desktop/&#x412;&#x41a;&#x420;/&#x43c;&#x430;&#x442;&#x435;&#x440;&#x438;&#x430;&#x43b;%20&#x43f;&#x440;&#x43e;&#x432;&#x435;&#x440;&#x435;&#x43d;&#x43d;&#x44b;&#x439;/66.txt</Value>
</Feature>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">MimeType</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String">text/plain</Value>
</Feature>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">docNewLineType</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String"></Value>
</Feature>
</GateDocumentFeatures>
<!-- The document content area with serialized nodes -->

<TextWithNodes><Node id="0"/>"<Node id="1"/>Toyota Australia unveils one-off eco car interior design in collaboration with First Base<Node id="90"/>", "There is no conversation causing a bigger stir in the fashion industry right now than sustainability. In the wake of Covid-19, and as consumers become more knowledgeable about the behind-the-scenes production of their clothes, designers and brands all over the world are refocusing their business models to put sustainability first&#x2014;and the automotive industry is taking heed. In fashion, the risks of waste and pollution generated by our industry lie in plain sight: it takes 2,700 litres to produce the cotton demanded by a single T-shirt; 190,000 textile microfibres land up in the ocean each year; 70 million oil barrels are used annually in order to produce polyester, and the list goes on. <Node id="789"/>The facts are alarming and the reality is hard to digest, but with savvy designers leading the way, using upcycled fabrics, innovating regenerative materials like ECONYL and implementing made-to-order business models to eliminate excess waste, the future of fashion is worth looking forward to. <Node id="1084"/>Or so says Alison Cotton, founder of sustainable activewear label First Base<Node id="1160"/>. Her brand is also behind Australia's first eco car interior design, aptly called 'auto couture', tailor-made for the Toyota Yaris Hybrid. In keeping with her approach to her own label, where her line of ethically-produced bike shorts, hoodies, sports bras and leggings is offered to consumers alongside vintage pieces and wellness products, Cotton has applied her environmentally-friendly know-how to develop an eco-conscious set of seat covers, floor mats, steering wheel and trims specifically made for the Toyota Yaris Hybrid. <Node id="1692"/>The eco car interior design is made entirely from locally sourced recycled nylon, and also makes use of pre-loved garments from the First Base label. The brand's 'X' logo is integrated into the design, as well as graphic stripes in red and off-white on the seats which give the design a sporty, energetic feel evocative of the Yaris Hybrid, and match the bold steering wheel in bright lipstick red perfectly<Node id="2099"/>. <Node id="2101"/>Bits of text, some reading 'use less' are mixed into the design of the seat covers, and serve as an incentivising reminder to minimise one's carbon footprint as much as we can<Node id="2276"/>. Of the design process, and working to outfit a car instead of a human body, Cotton reflects: "this was a totally new project for us so it was a fun process to take our vision and apply it in a new way. <Node id="2480"/>We've taken inspiration from heritage sports cars and blended that with our expression of sustainability and overall design ethos of laid back cool." The collaboration represents an effort both on Toyota and First Base's parts to highlight that style and sustainability can interact harmoniously, and need not compromise one another<Node id="2812"/>. Cotton says: "<Node id="2828"/>It's all about making positive changes in whatever way we can - whether that's big or small<Node id="2919"/>." She continues: "in my personal life I religiously use a keep cup, take my own bags when I grocery shop and try to purchase at bulk food stores with my own jars to reduce packaging wastage. I'm vegetarian (working towards veganism!), I vintage shop a lot instead of purchasing new or fast fashion... We just try to live a conscious life." Now, she's taken this mindset to the road, conscious her design skills can come in handy across industries, and are not limited to fashion."It's not perfect but I am a huge believer in everyone making a contribution," she says. "That's what adds up to something big." First Base and Toyota Australia have teamed up to create a one-off eco-design interior, to celebrate the launch of the new Yaris."<Node id="3658"/></TextWithNodes>
<!-- The default annotation set -->

<AnnotationSet>
</AnnotationSet>

<!-- Named annotation set -->

<AnnotationSet Name="Tactics">
<Annotation Id="1" Type="Mask" StartNode="1" EndNode="90">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="2" Type="Mask" StartNode="789" EndNode="1160">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="3" Type="RefAuthority" StartNode="1084" EndNode="1160">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="4" Type="PositiveEval" StartNode="1692" EndNode="2099">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="5" Type="Mask" StartNode="2101" EndNode="2276">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="6" Type="PositiveEval" StartNode="2480" EndNode="2812">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="7" Type="GoalSub" StartNode="2828" EndNode="2919">
</Annotation>
</AnnotationSet>

<!-- Named annotation set -->

<AnnotationSet Name="Original markups">
<Annotation Id="0" Type="paragraph" StartNode="0" EndNode="3658">
</Annotation>
</AnnotationSet>

</GateDocument>
