<?xml version='1.0' encoding='windows-1251'?>
<GateDocument version="3">
<!-- The document's features-->

<GateDocumentFeatures>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">gate.SourceURL</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String">file:/C:/Users/mosya/Desktop/&#x412;&#x41a;&#x420;/&#x43c;&#x430;&#x442;&#x435;&#x440;&#x438;&#x430;&#x43b;%20&#x43f;&#x440;&#x43e;&#x432;&#x435;&#x440;&#x435;&#x43d;&#x43d;&#x44b;&#x439;/75.txt</Value>
</Feature>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">MimeType</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String">text/plain</Value>
</Feature>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">docNewLineType</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String"></Value>
</Feature>
</GateDocumentFeatures>
<!-- The document content area with serialized nodes -->

<TextWithNodes><Node id="0"/>"<Node id="1"/>Meet 'My Way', the new <Node id="24"/>elegant scent<Node id="37"/> from Giorgio Armani<Node id="57"/>", "While it may be true that Covid-19 has upended our usual routines - with many of us working remotely and adapting to a new normal - the ritual of spritzing a fragrance onto the body before starting one's day is a calming constant in turbulent times. <Node id="311"/>Perfumes can affect our mood, rekindle our senses, help evoke our personality and, energetically, reset the kind of spirit or vibe we are communicating through scent. This is something Milanese luxury house Giorgio Armani knows well, and has carefully distilled in their newest offering from Armani Beauty, a floral fragrance called My Way<Node id="650"/>. <Node id="652"/>Designed to evoke a feminine inner confidence<Node id="697"/>, <Node id="699"/>underlined by a natural curiosity and desire for connection in one's personal journey, My Way was developed with sustainability in mind. Its multilayered notes are built out from climate-conscious ingredients sourced from all over the world. <Node id="941"/>Think a hint of bergamot sourced from Italy's Calabria, as it fuses gently with orange blossom derived from Egypt. Then, a light and feminine mix of tuberose and jasmine gives the fragrance delicate nuance at its base. These meet the scent of cedar wood sourced from Virginia, white musks, and vanilla sourced from Madagascar<Node id="1266"/> that rounds out the scent's worldly-yet-elegant profile<Node id="1322"/>.<Node id="1323"/> It is at once reminiscent of travels past, able to conjure memories and write new ones, and forward-looking to a future where we can wander freely and explore the world, and ourselves, again<Node id="1514"/>. <Node id="1516"/>Not only future-facing in its curated palette of scents, sourced from all over the world, My Way also signifies Giorgio Armani's continued sustainability efforts and commitment to fight climate change. The fragrance's bottle is easily refillable, designed with recycled and recyclable materials, and so can be proudly displayed in one's bathroom cabinet or beauty shelf for years to come<Node id="1903"/>. <Node id="1905"/>It is carbon neutral and in step with Armani Beauty's wider 5-year action plan to achieve carbon neutrality across all of its products by 2025 and reduce its carbon footprint by 25%<Node id="2086"/>. As Giorgio Armani reflected in a press release: "I believe that environmental issues should be close to everyone's heart, now more than ever. There is no way we can ignore the fact that the future of the younger generations depends on our choices." That's why the luxury house has aligned with actress Adria Arjona, who fronts the campaign, and whose own ethos aligns with that of My Way - which sees elegance, individuality and a sustainability-first mindset coalesce in a philosophy defined by 'I am what I live'. <Node id="2604"/>Speaking to Arjona's appointment as the face of My Way, and a new face of Armani Beauty, Armani said: "Adria Arjona is a traveler, a young woman of today; intelligent, curious, free of prejudice, independent, and capable of treasuring every life experience. <Node id="2862"/>She is a citizen of the world, who thanks to her authentic experiences and encounters can truly say: I am what I live." Now, with a spray or two of your own bottle of My Way, you can too<Node id="3048"/>. My Way is available to buy here."<Node id="3083"/></TextWithNodes>
<!-- The default annotation set -->

<AnnotationSet>
</AnnotationSet>

<!-- Named annotation set -->

<AnnotationSet Name="Tactics">
<Annotation Id="1" Type="Mask" StartNode="1" EndNode="57">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="2" Type="EmotionalSetup" StartNode="24" EndNode="37">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="3" Type="GoalSub" StartNode="311" EndNode="650">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="4" Type="GoalSub" StartNode="652" EndNode="697">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="5" Type="PositiveEval" StartNode="699" EndNode="1322">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="6" Type="EvalTransfer" StartNode="941" EndNode="1266">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="7" Type="EmotionalSetup" StartNode="1323" EndNode="1514">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="8" Type="PositiveEval" StartNode="1516" EndNode="1903">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="9" Type="AbstrStats" StartNode="1905" EndNode="2086">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="10" Type="GoalSub" StartNode="2862" EndNode="3048">
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="11" Type="RefAuthority" StartNode="2604" EndNode="3048">
</Annotation>
</AnnotationSet>

<!-- Named annotation set -->

<AnnotationSet Name="Original markups">
<Annotation Id="0" Type="paragraph" StartNode="0" EndNode="3083">
</Annotation>
</AnnotationSet>

</GateDocument>
